Chloe Chou

chloechou.com/portfolio chloechoudesign@gmail.com 310 906 8920

About Me

Hello there! I'm Chloe. I am a product designer with a diverse skill set ranging from the creative to the technical, with a strong passion to create useful, engaging and meaningful interactions.

Tools

Figma InVision
Sketch Zeplin
Adobe XD Miro
Adobe Photoshop Webflow
Adobe Illustrator HTML/CSS

Skills

Interaction Design Usability Testing
Visual Design Design Thinking
Wireframing Design Handoff
Prototyping Front-End Development
User Research

Education

B.F.A., Communication Design

Texas State University Dean's List 2011, 2012

Full-Stack Web Development

UCI Continuing Education
December 2017

Experience

Product Designer at JibJab

Los Angeles, CA • Nov 2020 - Present

- Visual Design, Web Design, App Design, UI/UX, Ideation, Prototyping for SYBooks experience, JibJab App & Web iterations, and JibJab Invites MVP.
- Preps and Exports key components and assets to Dev Teams.
- Monitors Development Progress, provides Visual Audits as needed.
- Design for SYBooks Marketing: Email templates, online promos.
- Evolves Design System and Style Guide.

Product Designer & Front-End Developer at SunStreet

Irvine, CA • Jun 2018 - Nov 2018

Design and code visually appealing and on-brand responsive website assets using front-end code in HTML, CSS, JQuery, and JavaScript to interface with backend code. Maintain multiple websites using WordPress, Shopify and OctoberCMS to edit/create pages. Create and maintain email campaigns in MailChimp.

Web Designer at Asia Fusion Technology

Taipei, Taiwan • Jun 2014 – Mar 2017

Designed digital products for clients in a wide variety of industries in a highly collaborative setting. Responsible for creating concepts, visual directions, executions and ensuring final delivery.

Freelance Visual Designer at R/GA

New York, NY • Nov 2013 - Feb 2014

Designed digital products for clients in a wide variety of industries in a highly collaborative setting. Responsible for creating concepts, visual directions, executions and ensuring final delivery.

Graphic Design Intern at Moment

New York, NY • May 2013 - Aug 2013

Collaborated closely with experience designers, senior designers and principles to design interfaces for mobile devices with an emphasis on user needs. Designed a new application concept—Compass, that aimed at enhancing the visitor experience at Bronx Zoo by leveraging the capability of wearable technologies, Google Glass.